{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862584084","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862584084"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862586609","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862586609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862592268","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862592268"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862595810","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862595810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862598289","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862598289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862601330","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862601330"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862603818","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862603818"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862606240","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862606240"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862611586","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862611586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862631613","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862631613"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862637039","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862637038"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862640618","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862640618"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862646338","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862646338"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862650681","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862650681"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862653463","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862653463"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862656517","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862656517"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862660477","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862660477"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862662809","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862662809"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862686418","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862686418"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuliita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862691317","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862691317"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuliita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862695440","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862695440"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuliita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862698928","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862698928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuliita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862703224","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862703224"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuliita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862706595","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862706595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuliita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862709463","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862709463"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuliita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862719687","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862719686"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alisema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862723014","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862723014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alisema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862725896","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862725895"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alisema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862728746","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862728746"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alisema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862732602","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862732602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alisema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862736210","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862736210"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alisema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862738582","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862738582"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alisema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862752056","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862752055"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kipekee"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862755881","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862755881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kipekee"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862759827","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862759827"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kipekee"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862763802","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862763802"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kipekee"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862769504","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862769504"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kipekee"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862774228","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862774228"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kipekee"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862781972","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862781972"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kipekee"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862790228","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862790228"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kipekee"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862793778","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862793777"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kipekee"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862819075","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862819074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sherehe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862823081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862823081"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sherehe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862826921","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862826920"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sherehe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862832317","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862832316"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sherehe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862836904","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862836904"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sherehe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862840528","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862840528"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sherehe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862843771","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862843771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sherehe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862852532","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862852532"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alikata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862855031","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862855031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alikata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862857240","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862857240"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alikata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862862355","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862862354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alikata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862865483","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862865483"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alikata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862868764","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862868764"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alikata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862871012","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862871012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alikata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862882432","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862882432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mawimbi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862884425","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862884425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mawimbi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862887208","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862887207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mawimbi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862888991","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862888991"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mawimbi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862895105","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862895105"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mawimbi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862898595","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862898595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mawimbi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862901931","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862901931"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mawimbi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862910906","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862910906"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akitela"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862914698","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862914698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akitela"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862916832","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862916832"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akitela"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862921039","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862921039"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akitela"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862925012","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862925012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akitela"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862927852","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862927852"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akitela"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862931326","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862931326"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akitela"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862962919","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862962919"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_maanake"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549862999665","data":{"timestamp":" 1549862999665"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_maanake"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863003834","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863003834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_maanake"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863006472","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863006472"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_maanake"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863013937","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863013937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_maanake"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863017100","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863017100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_maanake"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863024185","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863024184"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_maanake"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863028249","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863028249"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_maanake"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863048006","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863048005"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_maanake"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863054752","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863054751"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 54f6574f-f733-4ace-a8b9-537525946f75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_maanake"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863091686","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863091685"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863096468","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863096468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863101552","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863101552"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863112046","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863112046"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863115907","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863115907"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863118533","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863118533"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863129137","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863129137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863136147","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863136147"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863138840","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863138840"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863162847","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863162847"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_anaitwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863167259","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863167259"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_anaitwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863173106","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863173106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_anaitwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863181389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863181389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_anaitwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863190751","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863190751"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_anaitwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863199003","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863199003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_anaitwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863212385","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863212385"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_anaitwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863220007","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863220006"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_anaitwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863225999","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863225999"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_anaitwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863237210","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863237210"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_anaitwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863240174","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863240174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_anaitwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863245725","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863245725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_anaitwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863277928","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863277928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mishale"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863281851","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863281851"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mishale"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863285626","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863285626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mishale"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863288707","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863288707"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mishale"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863295433","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863295433"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mishale"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863298228","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863298228"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mishale"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863301923","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863301923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mishale"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863305046","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863305046"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mishale"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863331579","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863331579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akasema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863338653","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863338653"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akasema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863346947","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863346947"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akasema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863350739","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863350739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akasema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863357706","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863357706"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akasema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863365800","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863365800"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akasema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863374136","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863374136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akasema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863381629","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863381628"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akasema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863388418","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863388418"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akasema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863393369","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863393368"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akasema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863400136","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863400136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akasema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863402149","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863402149"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akasema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863407108","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863407108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akasema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863411113","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863411113"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akasema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863431569","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863431569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_umeiona"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863438097","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863438097"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_umeiona"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863447044","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863447044"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_umeiona"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863453638","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863453638"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_umeiona"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863459539","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863459538"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_umeiona"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863466295","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863466295"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_umeiona"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863475653","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863475653"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_umeiona"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863482630","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863482630"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_umeiona"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863487595","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863487595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_umeiona"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863494481","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863494480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_umeiona"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863502976","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863502976"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_umeiona"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863511354","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863511354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_umeiona"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863516081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863516081"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_umeiona"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863539437","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863539437"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mitaani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863540583","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863540583"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mitaani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863553255","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863553255"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mitaani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863559256","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863559255"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mitaani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863559838","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863559837"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mitaani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863574331","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863574331"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mitaani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863578530","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863578530"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mitaani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863579386","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863579385"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mitaani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863589016","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863589016"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mitaani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863594576","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863594576"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mitaani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863594776","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863594776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mitaani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863601508","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863601508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mitaani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863607511","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863607511"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mitaani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863614485","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863614485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mitaani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863614496","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863614496"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mitaani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863620063","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863620063"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mitaani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863626413","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863626413"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mitaani"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863639624","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863639624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kumpata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863649812","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863649812"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kumpata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863658449","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863658449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kumpata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863665491","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863665490"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kumpata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863673240","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863673240"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kumpata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863682583","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863682583"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kumpata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863690933","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863690933"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kumpata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863703131","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863703130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kumpata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863718279","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863718279"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kumpata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863724935","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863724935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863725901","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863725901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" ","":"<empty>"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863733713","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863733713"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863745887","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863745886"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863759144","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863759144"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" X"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863771540","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863771540"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863772149","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863772149"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863779178","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863779177"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863794081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863794081"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863795081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863795081"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863809590","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863809590"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863819548","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863819548"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863820436","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863820436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863829114","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863829114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863829202","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863829202"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863832588","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863832588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863851322","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863851322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" X"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863870136","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863870136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863882085","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863882085"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863882799","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863882799"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863926968","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863926968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863943287","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863943286"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549863986678","data":{"timestamp":" 1549863986678"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864025045","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864025045"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 8dadbc9f-f226-4da9-9c49-a953a4f89b70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_ameenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864061867","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864061867"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 4be5d1df-ee7d-437c-9092-3fb29f0f440a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864062551","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864062551"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 4be5d1df-ee7d-437c-9092-3fb29f0f440a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864063505","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864063505"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 4be5d1df-ee7d-437c-9092-3fb29f0f440a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864063698","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864063698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 4be5d1df-ee7d-437c-9092-3fb29f0f440a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864064292","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864064292"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 4be5d1df-ee7d-437c-9092-3fb29f0f440a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWITU"," userResponse":" MWITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864065026","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864065026"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 4be5d1df-ee7d-437c-9092-3fb29f0f440a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864065450","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864065450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 4be5d1df-ee7d-437c-9092-3fb29f0f440a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864066033","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864066033"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 4be5d1df-ee7d-437c-9092-3fb29f0f440a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864078581","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864078581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 4be5d1df-ee7d-437c-9092-3fb29f0f440a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864081960","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864081959"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 4be5d1df-ee7d-437c-9092-3fb29f0f440a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864086243","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864086243"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 4be5d1df-ee7d-437c-9092-3fb29f0f440a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864086542","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864086542"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 4be5d1df-ee7d-437c-9092-3fb29f0f440a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864088424","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864088424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 4be5d1df-ee7d-437c-9092-3fb29f0f440a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864088510","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864088510"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 4be5d1df-ee7d-437c-9092-3fb29f0f440a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864143813","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864143812"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 98c7fcc5-4797-4a13-9095-0da6d0796646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864144048","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864144046"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 98c7fcc5-4797-4a13-9095-0da6d0796646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864145025","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864145024"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 98c7fcc5-4797-4a13-9095-0da6d0796646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864146310","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864146309"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 98c7fcc5-4797-4a13-9095-0da6d0796646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864149231","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864149230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 98c7fcc5-4797-4a13-9095-0da6d0796646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864150094","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864150094"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 98c7fcc5-4797-4a13-9095-0da6d0796646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864150417","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864150416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 98c7fcc5-4797-4a13-9095-0da6d0796646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864151664","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864151663"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 98c7fcc5-4797-4a13-9095-0da6d0796646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864155203","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864155202"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 98c7fcc5-4797-4a13-9095-0da6d0796646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864156196","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864156195"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 98c7fcc5-4797-4a13-9095-0da6d0796646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864156457","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864156457"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 98c7fcc5-4797-4a13-9095-0da6d0796646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864157411","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864157411"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 98c7fcc5-4797-4a13-9095-0da6d0796646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864160328","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864160328"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 98c7fcc5-4797-4a13-9095-0da6d0796646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864161373","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864161373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 98c7fcc5-4797-4a13-9095-0da6d0796646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864161855","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864161854"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 98c7fcc5-4797-4a13-9095-0da6d0796646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864166453","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864166452"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 98c7fcc5-4797-4a13-9095-0da6d0796646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549864166541","data":{"timestamp":" 1549864166541"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_082225"," gameId":" 98c7fcc5-4797-4a13-9095-0da6d0796646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}